(Raj:)three...
(Sheldon:)two...
(Amy:)one.
(Dave:)That's too bad.
(Howard:)Maybe we did make the test
too difficult.
(Raj:)I don't think it matters.
Look, Sheldon,
(Raj:)I believe when the time is right
for you to meet someone,
(Raj:)it'll just happen.
(Raj:)Okay? Not because of
a test or a Web site,
(knocking)
but because...
We are the dreamers of dreams!
(Howard:)It's an actual girl,
and she's really pretty.
Answer it!
(Sheldon:)All right.
(Sheldon:)Can I help you?
Um, a-are you the physicist that
placed the ad on Craigslist?
(Sheldon:)Yes.
(Girl:)Hi. I'm Vanessa Bennett.
(Girl:)Sorry it took a while
for me to get here.
(Girl:)I was stuck in this
boring symposium
(Girl:)on atomic spectroscopy
when I came across your ad,
(Girl:)and it saved my night.